*STARTER PACK <Only single-block lodestones and floor magnetic sources>

@ Legend:
M - Floor Magnetic source
m - Off Magnetic source
█ - Walls (Boundaries)
e - Exit
s - Start
b - Button 1		f - Button 2
D - Door 1			F - Door 2
xyzXYZ - To dictate which lodestone to put. Group same characters together to indicate that they are parts of the same lodestone. Only applies when they are adjacent to each other. Lowercase = pushable. Uppercase = unpushable. Refer to the more complex levels for their usage. 
@

One way path demonstration
███████████
███XXX█████
█s x     e█
█████M█████
███████████

